# Preeti Vishwakarma

### Commercial Territory Representative

Over a rapidly progressive career of 7 years in qouta carrying role, today I believe in SPIN Selling and value selling. I have been always an achiever to my targets and is always determined towards my work. I have created a good spirit between the customers, partners and maintained highly effective customer rapport.

preeti90v@gmail.com	$\bowtie$
9071409494	
Bangalore, India	Q
linkedin.com/in/preeti-v-85945547	in

#### **SKILLS**

Rapport Building on	the Call Negotiation	Negotiation Gaining Commitment Closing Techniques				
Pre & Post-Sale Rela	tionship Management	Social	Selling	Lead C	ualification	Forcasting
Customer Success	Strategic Prospectin	g Skills	Adaptal	ble Se	elf Motivated	/ Ambitious
Critical Thinking/Problem Solving Digital Transformation Journey						

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Commercial Territory Representative NetApp India

NetApp India 07/2018 - Present

Data Center Solutions

Bangalore, Karnataka,India

#### Tasks

- This is a customer-facing and quota-carrying role where I am responsible for selling the complete NetApp solutions and services within a territory. This is driven by both partner ecosystems or managing the customers directly.
- I am also strategizing NetApp entry with all high, medium, and low touched accounts by engaging with different levels of CXOs and understanding their existing infrastructures. Overall developing a GTM plan for a set of customers and territory, focusing on long-term value.
- I work closely with the SE team for the creation of BOM,POCs, the Marketing team for MDFs plans and campaigns, Support team for post-sales gueries,legal team for tendering and legal agreements.
- Driving the business through the channel partners, Distributors for both Cloud services and other NetApp data center soutions mainly related to storage. Enriching the partners and distributors about new updates for Inprem & on cloud solution with AWS, GCP, and MS Azure, supporting them for a sales pitch.
- Work closely with Global System Integrators (GSIs), SI (System Integrators) VAR (Value Added Resellers) and qualifying new partners and keep on adding multiple qualified VARs quarter on Quarter.
- Working closely with strategic alliances partners like CISCO, Veeam, Rubrik, commvault, and many more.
- Implementing the partner-led marketing events (online and offline) that are customer-centric and deliver customer demand, revenue growth, and positively impact brand equity.
- Use Salesforce to update the Opportunities, LinkedIn Navigator Tool, LUSA, Hubspot, and other internal applications to nurture potential accounts. Till date, I have created a strong sales pipeline and have given a well-defined week forecast to the management.
- Always achieved my guota and added large number of NNA year on year.
- Forecast weekly/Monthly/quarterly with sales pipeline and closures also presented the right forecast in every QBRs to the stakeholder and showcasing what worked and what not and coming up with new strategies on how to we can encourage accounts and regions and support required for it.

Acheivement: FY19 - 130% -

Closure - \$700k+deal size, F20-Last Quarter closure-\$1.2 M, FY21: 1.2 M, Made 1st closure for SPOT by NetApp for the Country(recent)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Sr. Sales Executive

#### PayPal Inc (Client) - Altimetrik India Pvt Ltd

12/2016 - 06/2018

Bangalore, Karnataka, India

#### Tasks

- Quota carrying role to acquire new seller and maintaining targeted revenue generation base. (up-sell/cross-sell).
- Finding our the right merchant by qualifying there websites, hosting vendors and other services like wordpress, shopify etc.
- Meeting them in person to understand the complexity of their business and corroborating it with SaaS products and making as the "Only Choice" for the Payment gateway.
- Acted as merchant's advocate when escalating and resolving issues technical issues incorporation with the engineering team.
- Managing and updating the sales pipeline in the Salesforce (CRM) to secure the leads.
- Working closely with the internal decision-makers and external Stakeholders. IE. Owner or CFO of the retailer or the seller as a proprietorship.
- Presidencies on complex closures, specifically with large merchants and responsible for their onboarding them
- Adequacy in E-commerce markets of different sectors, track record in Customer Life Cycle Management and operations.
- Efficient Knowledge in the different segments: Jewelry, apparel, Fashion Designer, Electronic Goods, Tours, and Travel, etc.
- Acheivement :Net New Marchants onboard-15 Nos | Achieved new transaction Targets \$150K per Quarter

#### Sales Associate

Microsoft India(Client)- NDS Infotech.

05/2015 - 12/2016 Bangalore, India

#### Tasks

- This is a quota-carrying role, meeting the customer to understand their complexities on projects and providing the right product as an Enterprise Project Management tool.
- Have supported most of the Big-ticket size customers and coordinating with Pre-sales team for BOM, POC, installation detailings.
- Worked closely with Microsoft team for nurturing the targeted customers for the closer of the deals on given committed week/month.
- Submission of the proposal,negotiation and keen involvement in supporting the team for the installation of the products & services.
- Infested almost every sector of south India: Defense Services, IT/ITES, Pharma, e-commerce, and manufacturing, BFSI, Public sector.
- Handling the threat from identified competitors and prepared the strategies according to the product.
- Act as a relationship manager for the prevailing customers to reach the technical expert and other departments.
- I also created a healthy relationship with the CIO and other CXO to get there upcoming demands and try to push internally to complete it asap.

Acheivement: Successful completion of AOP Goal: 500K for H1 & H2 (\$1M/Year)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Branch Sales Coordinator - South and West India ISS Facility Services India Pvt Ltd.

07/2013 - 04/2015 Pune/Bangalore,India

Tasks

- Making cold calls, lead generations and targeting the big size tickets accounts to full fill the benchmark.
- Also maintained the Sales Pipeline with Add On business and Portfolio business for the region.
- Preparation of quotation and bidding for different manufacturing and Govt sectors.
- Outsourced the software like a cloud like SAP, ERP, and other offerings like Tally, OEMs as well for BFSI, Manufacturing, IT, Hospitals, Education Institutes.
- Preparation of MIS containing, details of new accounts, add business, pending billing from different customer.
- Coordinating with operation Team for vendors for proper delivery of materials at the site for the implementation of the new Projects and sites.

Acheivement: Given multiple Key Account - Acheived AOP - 150k\$ /monthly

#### **EDUCATION**

Master In Business Administration-Marketing University of Pune

2011 - 2013 Pune, Maharashtra, India

**Bachelor's In Computer Applications** Utkal University

2009 - 2011 Bhubaneshwar, Odisha, India

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Helping Client Succeed - FranklinCovey (01/2019)

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Second Edition): AWS Integrated Services (02/2019 - 01/2020)

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Second Edition): AWS Core Services (05/2019 - 04/2020)

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Second Edition): Introduction to the AWS Cloud (02/2019 - 01/2020)

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (Recently)

Google Ads Certification - Going On

### **LANGUAGES**

Hindi English Gujarati Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency

Kanada Mandarin

Limited Working Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency

#### HONOR AWARDS

Outstanding Achievement Q3- 2017

PayPal Inc

### **INTERESTS**

Badminton | Running | Cricket | Cycling | Weight Lifting | Camping

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## **Volunteering Training** Akshaya Patra Foundation

2019 - Present

The Akshaya Patra Foundation is a non-profit organisation in India that runs school lunch programme across India

India

## **REFERENCES**

References available upon request